Well, let's move on to business management systems
.
As always, let's take a
look to see where we are.
We go to Damdown, we go to
second, we go to business management systems
and okay, we
have identification.  Uh, similar
to what we were discussing a
while ago in
intermodular projects,
well of course, what are they in the case of
developing a business management system
?  What are the licenses
under which you can license it?
Well, for example, okay, so you can see
that in the end everything is related.  Let's
see what the chat brings up.  Okay, perfect.
Good.  Hey, let's see.
We were talking about the
installation issue, okay?  We were talking
about, okay, verification and of course,
documentation of the operations
carried out, okay?  This is where we're going to
start using the tool we
started creating yesterday, okay?  the
tool we created in
management systems, sorry, in
data access, where once again this is
where the subjects begin to
connect.  Hey, let's see what the
latest version of the app we
had so far is.  We had the
views, we had the canvas, this is
where we left off in the previous class.
Okay, perfect.  And we had this part
here, right?  So I'm going to go back to what
we did yesterday.
I'm going to go to data access.
I'm going to move on to
connector management, not
file management, working with files,
exercises.
We are going to
return instead of print.
And I, for example, what I'm
going to do next is tell it that instead of
wanting the entire structure of D,
we're going to extract
the folder.
Come on, go on.
Well, what I want is DAM second
EU programming business management systems
installation
modules, exercises,
Canban.  Okay, I want this as default for
now.
I click here.
What I'm going to do in this case is
that I'm going to transfer it to documentation.
Therefore, Cambana application.
Where are you?
No. Modules,
Canvan exercises,
okay?  I'm going to move it to
documentation.
Here,
here I'm going to do 01 exercises.
Yes. Let's see.  Okay.  Hey, Fran,
Fran, see what you're telling me?
Okay, I can imagine, I can imagine what the
problems are, but you tell me and we'll
take a look at them and fix them.
So, uh, I'm going to put some
documentation here,
so I come this way, I come this way, I
come this way.
Okay.  And inside documentation
I'm going to create a folder called
documentation.
I'm chatting, okay?  I'm telling
you and when you can,
tell me either in writing or by
micro.  I can imagine what you're going to tell me.
I'm going to ask you next, uh, to
tell me your subject, uh, I'll ask for your
ID to enter the submission panel,
okay?  And I'm telling you.  And you tell me and we'll
take a look at it.
Okay?  So, in documentation, now
I'm going to
file management, I'm going to second, I'm
going to business management systems, I'm
going to identification, I'm going to
documentation,
and in documentation I'm going to create a
file called a documenter.   Let's
see, I have the speaker on.
Yes, correct.  Okay, so Fran, tell me, I
guess you'll be writing.  Okay,
so what I'm going to do now is
say that I want to
recover the contents of the W folder,
that is, from the folder back.
Oh, and we're going to see it.  Let's see what this
gives me.
So if I run this
in documentation, in documenter,
I'm going to run Python 3 documenter
and there we have it.  Okay, and as we can
see, I have an extract,
I have an extract
of everything that I have up to
this point.  I don't know what this data is
right now, which I also
tell you, ah, that data was the JSON that had
the information.  Okay, perfect.
This tri.xml, XML.  Well, I do
n't want it to be called tri,
but I want it to be called
documentation.Mmd.
Okay?  So
this is going to be,
let's see, this is second
data access.
Business management systems.  Let's go to
documentation.   Let's
go here.   Let's
go to the documentation
and really really this exercise,
let's see it,
okay?  This is tree tree
.  Python
and this is
documentation.
Python.
So, in Python documentation,
what I'm going to do is I'm going to remove
this,
I'm going to take this
and I'm going to say from, let's
see,
from tree.
Let's see draw.
I'm going to say from
tree
import.
draw.
Okay, we use the route, it's this
three lines is this.  And now what it does
is that on one hand it prints it and on the
other hand it takes it to file.
Okay, so
this over here,
this over here.
And now I'm going to call this file,
for example, since we named
this
previous software,
login,
log in
index.
We haven't given it a name,
which I find quite strange,
so perhaps it's time to give it a
name.  You already know that the fact
is that I remember choosing a color.
I'm going to common, I'm going to style.
The color we chose was steel blue,
but of course, I already have steel blue, I
think, for a program, so I don't know, I
'd have to give it a name, but okay.
In documentation
I'll call it .Md
execute.
Let's see, let's see.  All right,
Fran, see you.  Oops.
Ah, okay.
Okay,
Fran, let's see it.  I'll read you first.
Okay, okay.  Yes, correct.  Fran, give me
your ID
so I can enter.
Let's see.
Okay,
Fran, don't worry.
I'll fix that zero, because remember that I
always tell you that behind the AI ​​there is
a human being,
so
let's see.  I eval.jocarsa.com.
Okay.  Okay.  So, programming
services and processes, but when you get in there are
no lessons.  Okay, perfect.  There are no
lessons.  Let's see a second one.
Uh, here
I go to HTML, I go to Eval,
I go to
DB, I go to repositories, I go to
uh,
gee.
Ah, here's the problem.  Okay, it's not
there, that's why there are no lessons.
Okay, okay.  Now I'll tweak this later and
then the lessons will appear to you.
Okay, in the meantime,
next question.
Uh, I go into
localhost, I go into Eval,
okay?  I'm going to eh interfaces,
interface development.
Okay.  I'll take your ID,
okay?  Okay.  And it looks like this one and I
see a zero here.  Okay, let's see as a
student.
Okay.  Introduction and contextualization.
Uh, in this project I created, I
used llama, okay?  This is
about tools for
automatic care, right?
Develop the frontend, okay?  Okay.
Okay.
Okay.  Okay.  Okay.
Very good.  Okay.  Because?
Take.  Obviously this is not correct.
Okay.  Well, to start with, there's some
kind of problem here because
the evaluation didn't occur on two of the engines,
and on the third engine, the evaluation
occurred, but it gave an error.  Something something
is obviously wrong, okay?
So I'm going to do the following.
What I'm going to do here is
delete your review.  Just a moment.
I hope without ruining the
entire exercise.  Let's see it.  I delete the
evaluation.  Okay, here I do it like this
and okay.  And I have your answer saved,
but I haven't evaluated it, that is, I have
ruined the evaluation.  Okay, okay.  No,
yes, apart from that, Fran, just so you know, just so you know
I have a Chrome.
Now I'm going to show it to you.
I have a Chrome that's taking up my
life called backup, where in
backup every hour that passes, every hour
I save a backup copy of all
your exercises, okay?  So,
just in case, if you
have it saved, it's better, but I have a
backup copy both
locally and on the remote server, okay?
So, okay.  So,
Fran, regarding that question,
obviously, obviously, based on what I
'm seeing here, that zero is an
error.  We had seen that even
directly other engines did not even appear
.  I send it for reevaluation and that's it
.  Okay, let's see more things.  In
interface development,
interface generation, error in statement.  Yeah,
okay, let's see.  For sure yes.
So in natural interface generation
, voice and speech, right?  Voice and
speech.  Okay, let's see.  So the
statement is this,
uh, see as a student.
Okay.  Ah, yes, it has uf Yes, yes, yes, yes.   He
's fried.  Okay, so look,
here what I'm going to do, Fran,
is that I have an
action here, this one, which is send to
trash, okay?  So I send it to the
trash, the activity disappears,
which means I'm forcing the
artificial intelligence to do something else,
and that happens from time to time,
right?  So, this is what I
told you, and I want you to always keep it very clear
and in mind: behind
artificial intelligence there is a
human being.  When you detect something that doesn't
fit, tell me and that's it.  And
humans always have the last word
over
artificial intelligence.  So that's it, nothing,
now then on the one hand I regenerate
activity, on the other hand I reevaluate and that's it
.  In fact, I was thinking about
adding a fourth
artificial intelligence, which is GPT OSS, the one from
this summer, the one they released this summer,
so, well, this weekend I
'd be testing it and seeing
how it goes.  And then I also
want to tell you that some students, a
group of students that I have in the morning
are giving me a lot of feedback.
So, a student told me, "Hey, it
seems like
artificial intelligence doesn't follow the rubric very much, it
seems like it doesn't take it very seriously."
And I said, "Okay, okay, no problem."
So, last night, late in the day, around
11:30 or 12, I was
modifying the software and I
told the software, hey, use the
full rubric and make sure that the students are
assessed according to the rubric.  Okay?
So the software said, "Yeah,
great, no problem, I'll
give you all a five."  And of course, I
panicked because the software started
giving all the students fives, but
fives as if to say, "Oh, since new
students haven't followed the
rubric faithfully, I'm taking points off."  And I was
like, "No, no, no, no, no, that's the
thing."  I mean, the point isn't to
take away points if they don't follow it
perfectly, but to give
points to those who do follow it and
all that.
So, last night I stopped the engine, I
returned it to how it was for this
weekend to finish tuning it
and wait, I want to drink
and nothing and start the
evaluation again.  What I'm trying to tell you with that is that
I estimate that in
a few weeks, this has a bit to do
with the intermodular project, because what I
'm doing is launching the
software and this week
things like this will surely happen and it's foreseeable
that in a few weeks
everything will be more fine-tuned, right?
Okay, so here we go.  Let's continue
well.  Well, I'll close here,
okay?  And about processes and services, I
know, I know.  He told me this
morning, I think it was Agustín, okay?
So, eh, well now I'll
see why they don't come out.
Eh, because the fact is that they have to leave.
The thing is, they have to leave,
but of course, just for a moment, since we're
here,
since we're here,
eh, okay.  Okay, development,
development, they don't come out.
So
I'm going to
use it, I'm going to scan the exercises.  and in
scan exercises,
processes,
services and processes.  Okay,
no, this is something else.
Processes.
This is yours,
okay?
HTML Bar D 2526 second programming of
services and processes.
And this goes to repositories, okay?  But
but I still need to
run the
Python 3 1 scan script exercises.
Okay.  And now we see how to
look at it, services and processes.  Now it
is there and now it is there.  Okay,
so well, right now it's
local.   I have
n't synced it with
the server yet, and now in a little while I'll
sync it, and well, in a little
while, tonight because we're in
class now, okay?  And you'll have access to
processes and services, okay?  Okay.
Come on, so we were here doing
this, RPMD,
so now what I want is let's
try it.
This was
this was in Neval here.  Okay,
ls.  Okay.  Python 3
documentation.
Okay.  A documentation file will have been generated
.
a file called ERPMD will have been generated
and the ERPMD file has this, right?
What we see, obviously, is the
file tree that the system has,
which means that right from the start I'm
going to save a lot of
code, a lot of manual work.  And
if
we now expand the software from this point on,
we will see that we will execute
documentation and the
system will automatically document itself.
Okay?  Let's build a
better markdown.  Okay, so now what I want
is for each of the items,
for each of the files, I want to
see the code for that file.  So,
let's see.
I have the tree here.
Okay,
so one thing you could do is
create
uh headers.  For example, this would be
header type H1, header type H2
and file type H3.  It would be an
option,
okay?  This would be an option.   Let's
go there.  Well, let's do that.
So what I'm going to
do next is if I have a tree
I'm going to come over here and Oh, not over here.  Where
are you?  Here.
Okay.
And I say,
create another script
to.  Let's see.
Eh, you instead of showing
a three
show eh no create
markdown
markdown headings
level of heading
in function to level of
depth of folder.
file,
okay?  So now next
this is out, I already have this.
And here in
documentation I'm going to create a
new file called eh headlines, headers,
headers.python
headers.python Python
what it's going to do is, that is, I will
then, obviously, first in
a markdown document I will put the index and
then I will put whatever else,
okay?  I'll put the markdowns.  Now
you'll see.
Okay.
And okay.
This is example use, okay?  So, I
go here, I go to headers, I remove the
main, I
remove the main and what I'm going to do is
uh
md lines print md lines okay, so
root is equal to this.
Root, this is header.
Okay, so I'll keep this,
I go to documentation
and then I say
f.Right.
Let's
let's do the following.
With openp.
Now in apen f mode.
And then I say
M of lines is this here.
I think I have too many sangrias here.
M of lines is this.  The address is the
path, the root.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.  F
right.  This is okay.  I really
want this.
Well, let's see.
Python.
Okay.  Draw marked.  Sure, sure.  Sorry.
From
from headers
import draw markdown.
We imported the bookstore.
Okay.  And eh cannot import name from
headers.
Okay.  Why not?  Because?  Ah, because I have
n't saved it.  Fantastic.  And this
was it.
Okay.  Save a return.  It's right.   I
execute.  Okay.  And if everything went well,
now I go to RPMD
and I have the index first.  And if all goes
well, oh, wow.   I
only have the index.  Let's see.
Well, another thing I can do, another
thing I can do is, hey, I've
closed it, right?  Don't be such a beast.
And therefore with the same one
with the same one here,
with the same one open, do two F rights,
okay?  Uh, maxp
root H1.  Okay, fine.
Very good.  This is cool.  So I run.
I'm going to RPMD.
No,
no, he's not doing anything.
Okay,
let's get
this out of the way.   Op
, op, op.  Where are you?  Here.
Okay,
very good.  Documentation.
I'm in the right place.
I'm running.  Yes. Documentation.
If I have it Let's
see.
Ah, print out.  Okay.
Okay.
Three lines is this.
Okay.   I
run
RP.
Wow,
interesting.
Fright three lines.  Ah, no, M for lines.
Gee, this is the thing.  Okay, I
was calling
MD lines.  Okay, now yes.
Very good.  Documentation.
I'm going back to RP.
Now yes.  This is true.
Good.  And if I have this.  Well, actually,
uh, I have previous, I have header, I have
CRM, I have desktop,
okay?  I even have a calendar and cards
and forms and graphs and Canvas,
okay, a database.
Pikach.  We will remove this later.
Okay, great.
This, obviously now I can release it
in eh DAM.  Second,
business management systems.
Identification,
documentation exercises documentation
documentation.
I'm going to RP.
Wow.  Ah yes, emojis.  Okay, yes.  And it's
just that
I'm not using UTF8.
Okay, but now in a moment
I'll put it in and that's fine.
What else do I need?  I like this for now
, but what
I'd like next is that apart from this, it has,
okay?, its own link and all that, no
problem.  Okay, what I would like is
that now, I also want to have the
code in markdown format for each
of
the files.  Let's see it.
Let's see it.
Let's see.  So, I'm coming
this way.
and I say,
"Okay, perfect. I like it
so much.
Now, please give
me uh
let's say
next to each file name,
file content. style
content within
markdown code
uh ticks tac tac tac to
open and tac tac tac to
close
accept only
a list of extensions of given extensions
current code is
and we go to headers, which are no longer going to
be just headers, but oh well.
And what we're going to do is in the
documentation first show, well,
now we'll also put the title and all
that, obviously, okay? But show the
title of the project, then the
tree, then the
markdown headers and within each header the
code. Let's go for it,
people.
Let's see it.
Wow. Okay, good. Fantastic. I didn't want
so many, but okay, I like it.
Let's see it.
And of course, and now what
we're going to do next is start connecting with
Oyama to get rid of the
heaviest part of the documentation, which is
basically, uh, having to make a
description of what
each of the  project files. So
the idea of ​​today's class, we have
a bit of class ahead of us, is to
have a system for generating
documentation
automatically first using Python,
combining it with what we saw yesterday about
data access and then also combining
that documentation system with an
artificial intelligence system to
avoid creating doc strings and
all that. Okay? So let's go here,
go to headers.
Hello, headers. Okay, let's see.
On the other hand, in documentation I
can already uncomment this.
So, I execute it,
we go to ERP and we have, let's see,
uh, there was a problem.
Retry.
Why? Why? What's happening? Let's
see. RP is 130 K.
Ah, well I don't know why. Ah, yes. Uh, let's
see. Ah, character encoding.
Edit anyway. Okay, yes.
Okay. Okay, there we have it. First we have
the list, then we have this and
then we have the code marked with
ticks. Okay, let's take a closer look. Let's take a
closer look.
And uh, let's see for a moment.
Let's see for a moment.
Here.
Let's see it here. Au. Au. Okay, now
we see this. Good. Yes.
The condition is met. Some part
escapes me. Well, CSS style.
There it seems to escape.
Okay. Style.
Okay.
Okay, this is good, but there's a lot that does
n't.
Okay. Okay.
Let's look for this in the document.
Let's see,
LED behavior status.
And if I do this,
right? Okay.
And if I want to see the original,
right? Okay, very good.
Uh,
it seems that markd
is not fully legal.
Maybe a problem of encoding. Please review
ticks.
Let's see it.
Now, next, as you can
imagine,
what I want is to pass a layer of
oyama to feed it each of the
files,
and tell it, "Give me
a comment on each of the
files." That is, give an
explanation, document each of the
files before the code, even if it
takes two or three hours until night or
whenever to document, but the idea
is that it is the software itself, whether
Artificial intelligence itself will
do it, right? Now, that heavy
documentation work, we
document today, but tomorrow we continue
developing, so the
documentation changes, so all that
heavy lifting will be done by
artificial intelligence. Okay, let's see.
Okay.
Let's see if there's any
company email in the meantime.
By the way, by the way, look, Gonzalo,
man, Gonzalo,
okay. Ah, well, look, this guy
is also a former student, so yes,
of course. I'll pass it on to him later.
Okay, I have a challenge. I have a challenge.
I have the email here. I
have the email,
okay? of this person. Wait, of this
person.
So this person,
who is Alva Moret, is a person who, for
two or three years now, I have
n't seen
that for years I've had a close
relationship with this person and a very good
relationship, and since I'm no longer involved in, let's
say, the business area
he's involved in, well, we no longer have a relationship.
Okay?
Okay, let's see, the statement is this.
Without any kind of commitment, I wanted to
ask you if  N8N
falls within your knowledge of your
guys, okay? Your knowledge
goes infinitely beyond N8N.
Uh, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know,
but, look, he's an architect,
okay? He doesn't know programming, but
I already know that for you guys, N8N is a
joke.
Three years ago, I sent him a former
SMR student named Vicente, who doesn't work
very well.
Uh, is there anyone this year who
specifically has knowledge of N8N?
Okay, I
want to send him someone. That someone
will work in automation
and probably in
artificial intelligence, but this Salva Moret,
uh, has a training center
and does architectural projects
and works with BIM, okay? He works with
Building Information Model, it's this one
here, okay? He'll
put his training center over here in a moment. Let's
see, wait a minute. This, okay? And
uh, what the hell, here, okay? He has this training center
and he's a really cool guy, okay? He's a
very  He's a tough guy, he's a guy who can open
a lot of doors. For me, over the years,
when I worked with him, he opened
a lot of doors for me by working with him, but
I want to because what he says is true,
okay? That the student I sent him didn't
work out at all and I have a
thorn in my side. I want the person
I send him this year to
be the best, okay? Because I want to make a
good impression with this person, because
3 years ago I made a bad impression, because I sent him
a student who didn't work out at all,
okay? And I'm telling you, and it wasn't
this guy's fault, it was the student's fault. I
know, there are other times when it's
Vale's fault, so
eh Fran, I mean, no, for what he
needs you're more than up to the task, okay?
So what I'm going to do and from
here on, well, I'll tell you and I'll
tell you all. Okay. Uh, it's that
really, let's see, eh, Salva Moret
talks about N8N because, I insist, because that
's what he knows, okay? Because it's
architect and doesn't work with other
tools, doesn't work with
programming languages.
I want to think, I insist, I'll
say it again, I haven't spoken to him in three years,
eh, but he's a guy who, I mean, he's
very focused, okay? and he's very
professional, and when he talks about N8N,
what he's talking about is eh automation, it's what you
want to automate, okay? So
, the idea is, I'll send you to this
company for an interview with whoever you want.
You go to the interview and
tell them, "Hey, José Vicente sent me about
this N8N issue and you
tell him, I can do much more than
N8N."
So, the question is, what do you need? I
mean, to see if what he needs
is for an architect to be able to automate and
we're talking about N8N or if what he
needs is automation. Okay? And I'm
telling you that what this guy works on,
which is architecture and BIM, lends itself
very well to automation, okay?
So, I  Well, for now, okay, Fran, I'm
going to send you and Josué and the rest
of the people you guys say, I'll send whoever
you say, okay? But what I will
tell you is that, uh, I mean, I want it to be
beneficial for both parties in the
sense that whoever gets involved with this
guy, when you see who he is, what he does,
that he has an architecture studio, that he
has a training center, what he does
in the architecture studio, you see
that he's a very powerful guy and I
also want to send him a
very powerful student, okay? And I want, as I
told you, 3 years ago the experience went badly
and I felt really bad because he's
a guy who for many years I've
had a good relationship with him and I want to
look good, okay? I want to look good, it
's not that you become his
slaves, okay? I want to look good
means that I know there's a
fruitful relationship for both parties,
that on the one hand the student does
cool things for this guy and on the other hand
what this guy can contribute to
you is also very  Okay, okay?
So, Fran, I'll compose
the email because this guy's email
isn't a quick email. I want to
sit down and write it properly and put it together properly
, okay? Because I'm telling you,
this person isn't just
anyone. So, let's see how it
went here. Okay, copy and send to:
Where are we? To headers.
Okay, okay. Let's try it.
RP Documentation.
Okay. Okay. Edit anyway.
And let's see because I haven't seen much of a
difference.
Okay. Well, what's this here?
Keyboard overlay.
What is this?
Let's see,
okay. We'll see this later.
index, php
doc type
header
style.
Okay, it's that it tells me this directly here
.
Of course, it could be a problem with how
I'm rendering. It could also
be,
well, no, right? And remark.
No, okay, we'll see later.
Okay, then this is where I'm seeing, you
see? This seizes as HTML a bunch of
code that doesn't render. Ah, can data. Okay
. Okay
. Okay.
Okay, come on.  So, what is this P? Okay,
P
is not in the list.
Python
P is not in the list and therefore should not
appear.
Okay, I'll tell you this, it's
rendering the HTML.
Let's see.
Here,
problems one, it is adding content
from files not in the list.
For example, Python two
, uh markd.
seems not to be being correctly rendered
.
Uh, HTML
is being
rendered
as HTML instead of doc,
instead of MDCD. Let's see. It
might be the renderer I have.
One way to find out is to go to GitHub
desktop, do a do a let's
see 25 26
do a push, see it with the
Jithhab renderer and see if that's where
the problem is.
Okay, so I'm going to Jithhub,
I'm going to repositories. Oh, look, 600. I'm
going to DAM 2526.
I'm going to second to make sure. I'm going
to I'm
going to enterprise management systems
, I'm going to identification, I'm
going to documentation, I'm going to
documentation,
RPMD documentation.
Okay.  Okay.
Ah, well this is even worse. Oh
my goodness, what a disaster.
Let's look at the code. The code is
fine,
but it seems to be a
rendering issue.
Let's see it.
[Music]
Okay,
I think the problem
is the relationship between the three elements.
So,
[Music]
And
okay, let's take this.
Okay, this is the use case.
Okay,
this is headers. I
can take the use case here.
Here I can take it here. This is
route.
And let's go there.
Generate,
recharge.
A little better. I think it's a
little better, but not entirely better.
Okay. Okay.
And I insist, I want to have this fixed
so that from there we can move on to the last
step of today's class, which that calls for.
But before that,
uh, probleming
for example,
okay?
from free files
in the project. To one.
Let's see.
This out. This
out. This out.
Okay.
One,
two,
three.
Uh,
it should render good markdown.
And then I think that here I  He'll say that
adding the backslash n to the documentation is
n't
very cool.
So let's take a look at it.
And as I said, the last step will be when
we get the
code right, to say, "Okay, but
now I need you to go into each
file.
Let's make a call first in
which we will pass the code of each
individual file
so that it makes a description of what is
in that file.  But then,
obviously, we'll have to make another
request that will be much more
computationally expensive,
in which we'll say, "I'll send you the entire
project so you can understand the entire
project, and now I'll send you a file
so you can not only tell me what that
file does, but also tell me what
that file does within the entire
project."  Okay?  Let's see.
And okay, okay,
okay.
Uh, no, not this.
Okay.
In tree,
in tree.
Okay.  Draw 3.
Okay.  Tree, lines.
Okay.  More or less.
Okay, next.
Three lines.
Three lines documentation.
Okay, next.
Use false emojis.  This makes me a little
less concerned.
Use
false emojis.  The thing is, I still want
emojis, but okay.  Good.  Make sure it
is UTF8.  Okay.
Okay.
Okay, let's see.
optional tree list at the start of the tree.
Hosts.  Okay.  Okay.  Fantastic.
Come on.
And I import that one.  Ah, very good.
Wow, it looks like I messed something up.
Okay, this is tree.
we execute.
Ok.
V
three lines
Dr.
I swear I had it updated,
but it seems I don't.
Let's see, DR 3.
Okay,
okay.
But well, not very okay.  Okay, at
least I'm not uploading anymore,
I'm not uploading all the files I don't
want to upload anymore.  Be careful because,
of course, PHP is not on the list.
Let's see it.  Headers.
Let's see what's allowed.
and eh default
PHP is there,
but it's
not putting it in.   It's
putting JavaScript in me, but it's not
putting PHP in me.
Curious.
Ah, I've seen it here before.
I've seen it here before.  Documentation.  Here it
is.
PHP.   We
run again.
We reload again.
Now grab PHP.
Okay.  Okay.  Well, here we go.
This is a matter of fine-tuning it later,
but what I want next is for it to
go into each file.
Let's see it.
Now.  Another file
to be called.
from headersp
to for each file
send
you or call
use quen
pass code
get eh
command from code
document entation
and add to the markd file
before that very block of code.
Okay, so now what I want is for
each file, as I'm telling you right
now, each file to be
passed to Oyama and say, "I'll give you this
code, give me back a comment,
some documentation, okay? So I know what
this file does, and I'm going to put it
into the documentation.
Let's see. Maybe now I'll try it with
something simpler
than this project, okay? A simpler file
or a simpler mini-project.
And as you can see, and as I'm saying, the goal
is to have documentation,
a documentation-generating software
such that you can
work with complete peace of mind, and
then you know you'll be able to
click on the software and the software will
automatically start generating
the documentation, even if it takes
a whole fight each time, but let
the software do it. Okay? What's it called?
Okay, I already have the pull. This isn't
necessary.
doc.python.
Okay, we put this here.
Very good.
And this, the idea is to modularize as much as
possible.
Okay.
Ah, very good. Code.
Okay. So, be careful with this because
from time to time it happens that the
same GPT chat escapes itself.
Code here goes and because it's a
Python format string
and that's it. Okay, then it passes the
prompt and now this is the prompt and now
how to integrate it into headers.
Okay,
please full headers.p Elbow guy.
for now what we'll see is that it will take
forever,
but oh well, no problem.
Let's see, I'm going to plug in the battery in the meantime
.
Okay, this is the main, no problem.
Okay, this is the headers,
so let's see what happens. Let's see if the
documentation explodes.
Let's take out
this one. Okay, we see how it is there. We
see how the CPU starts to pull. You
probably don't hear it, but the
fans have started moving.
The problem is, of
course, with this you wo
n't see the Markdown document.
There it is. Until it is generated. Until it is
finished generating.
I'm going to ask him to see if it's possible so I do
n't have to wait because it
can be thrown  hours quietly.
Okay.
Could it be possible
to write
as many operations as many right operations
needed to not have to
wait until the end to
see the document
but instead
write
eh each block as it is processed.
Okay, and so we don't need to
see all the documented software. If we
see two or three files, then
we get the idea that with more
time, it will do everything else.
More than anything because what I'm telling you,
because in the end we are documenting
dozens of files and it could
easily take, I don't know, 10 hours.
Okay, Mark's stream
streaming headers.
Okay,
this is strange to me because I thought he was
going to do the streaming in the
main file, in the
documentation.p file, but it seems not.
But anyway, whatever, I don't care
as long as he does it.
Maybe he has to modify both because
in the end, the one who writes
is really documentation, that's why it
surprised me a little, but let's
see.
Come on. Let's
Of course, that's it, it's exactly
what you say. I also tell you, Fran,
that between the version  7B and the
cloud version, there's a middle ground that I
'm not doing because I'm stupid, so I'm
telling you, which is eh Quen 7B on the GPU,
because what you just saw
shows that right now I
'm not using the GPU and therefore it could
go much faster because a Quen 7B
fits
on a graphics card like the one I have, but
yes, I know, I know. What happens is that
within that, ah, look, yes,
within that using the GPU, eh, sorry,
within that using the Cloud version, in
this case, given that Quen is an
open model, it doesn't entail as much
dependency as closed models and you
know that I don't like
dependency at all,
stream headers,
but it's still dependency,
okay? That's why you're going to see that obviously it
wouldn't be very easy to load
any provider's API and run with the API,
but I just don't want to. I want to do
everything. The more local and the more
independent the better. Because apart from that, let's
see, okay, because apart from that, in
job offers, eh, I mean, just with
that the guy  um, to Salvador Moret, you
go and tell him, "No, no, I
can set it up locally for you."
I mean, a server, a VPS, I don't know if he's
familiar with that part, I don't know if he's
using it in the cloud or he's using it or
knows that there's a community that can be
installed on a server, but that's why I
'm telling you, I mean, I want you to have a lot of
options at hand locally, because
I think that's a
very strong differentiation, very strong. Okay, let's
see. I'm going to stop this. I'm
going to stop this.
Okay, the RP will be reloaded. Ah, look,
how good. Okay, okay. How strange. Look,
Fran, he changed it for me and instead of
putting, you know, instead of putting
Asci, he put the characters you
told me about yesterday. But anyway, I don't care. Right
now I don't care at all.
So, I come over here, I click on
documentation.
Okay, look, now he's given me back the
emojis. It's really annoying.  And now
here we go. Let's go.
Okay, well, let's see
because if everything goes well now, in a
moment, if we see one or two, well, that's
enough for me, okay? We've already
achieved the objective and now, obviously, we
would have to wait,
okay?, either for everything to be done and then
improve it and give it a title and maybe
add images and then give everything, that
is, to whoever or to the model,
first give it the whole block and then
give it only the corresponding file,
but we know it's going to take a long time
. Okay, now we'll do it because since we have plenty of
time, now we'll do it and
at least we'll have it prepared and
then each one of you can
give it whatever you want,
but eh RPMD,
we'll see.
And yes, no, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, Fran,
it's just as you say, having to
leave it for a whole day and I
'm suffering right now,
but in quotes it's suffering for the better. I
'm suffering with you with the
issue of generating exercises,
correcting exercises, that  Everything is driven
by artificial intelligence, and you
can't imagine how many there are. Okay, for
the students I teach, and we're in the
first month,
for the students I teach, and right now,
exercises,
activities,
okay? There are 3,847,
so, as you can imagine,
that number is going to multiply by 10 between
now and the end of the course. That is, 30,000
activities. Imagine what it's like, I mean,
generating those 30,000 activities and
correcting those 30,000 activities with
artificial intelligence. But once
again, it's a pain because every
night it's time to see where the
artificial intelligence comes out, but it's
okay, okay? Because it's, let's say, like
a practice for what I want to show you later
in the intermodular project. Let's
see. Hey, come on, reload. We already have
one. Let's see it. Come on, what do you
think? Okay, index. PHP. This purpose
is the main page of an RP system
called José Vicente. Key functions,
start session, inputs, outputs,
side effects,  external dependencies,
approximate complexity, possible risks,
and cataplus. The exercise, okay? And the
code for back here. Now header. I do
n't know why it hasn't picked up
behavior. I've added
JavaScript files. I think the problem might
be there. Let's see what I can tell you. And no.
Ah, yes, yes, yes. JavaScript files.
Well, I don't know why. Okay, well, whatever
, okay? And CSS, okay? Purpose, you
define upper, inputs, outputs,
okay? And the CSS. And now it's in index.
Let's see it. Let's see it here. I
still don't get this. I don't care. I don't
care, but I don't care. Let's see, I don't know
if it's a UTF thing. No.
And it doesn't matter. I can't specify UTF.
Index. HPHP, then index php. Okay, now
CSS style, well CSS style, which I'll
tell you later, escapes the style. We'll
have to see why. Okay, but
CSS style and uh index php. There I tell you, it
's making a mistake in the in the interpreter
Markdown. The thing is,
theoretically, it's
fine, right? Theoretically, it
's fine, but there's something that's causing it to
slip. I don't know why, but, well,
let's, okay, let's do the triple
somersault.
So now I'm going to say, "Okay,
I like it, but you're commenting on every
file without knowing what the rest of the
project does.
So now I say to him, I'm going to
stop." Okay, this is red. Okay, come on,
I'm going to stop
and
let's see it.
And now I say,
okay, I like it a lot. But
on passing file
toama
and preparing
prompt.
Let's make this pass the
entire project
with folders, subfolders, files, contents,
etc.
I mean
structure
and then pass that each particular file
and ask
not only for documentation
of that verif
Oyama
of understanding the
role of the file inside the whole
of the project,
okay? That is, we pass him not only the
file, but we also pass him the entire
project so that he calls you. It's as if
someone tells him, "Document this
file and he tells you, okay, but this
file, I mean, who else it goes with, what it
does." It's like, "No, no, I'll give you this
file and that's it." Well, well, I'll
tell you what's in the file, but I
can't tell you the role it plays in
the project because I don't know. Well, right now it
calls is the same. Okay?
Therefore, what  In this case,
tell him that I'll pass you the entire project, I'll
pass you the file, tell me about the file,
but also tell me from the point
of view of what it does in the project.
Okay, well, extended. Okay.
Okay. Same as before.
Same as before. This. Okay. It will have
stopped there halfway. Okay. And
doc. There I do it like this. Okay,
the code is this.
Now the quiet code is this.
Okay. Uh, code, code, code. Okay,
usage.
Okay.
Please fill this out.
Code, of course, tradeofs, obviously
the token size is going to go through the roof,
okay? I mean, the token size is going to go up,
but come on, a lot. So, we
can tell him,
well, maybe we can cut or
maybe we can prune, okay? Performance.
Now each file takes the entire
project and this is going to slow you down a
lot.
You should cache the context once,
okay?
And if it's too big, well, the
truth is, it's true that uh, I pass
each and every one of the  times the entire
project, well it would probably be more
efficient to cache it and reuse the
cache, but well, okay. Okay, that's
clear, you're right.
Okay.
Okay,
this is, wait,
this is stream headers, okay?
I don't remember stream headers like that,
but well, whatever.
Okay. Okay.
Content. It
's funny. And here
and here.
Okay, so let's go.
Let's go. I'm going to documentation and if it
doesn't break,
let's see it.
I'm going here. Hey, I saved this,
right?
Okay,
previous index. Wait a second, I'm going
to stop, I'm going to start again because I
hadn't saved a file.
I'll make sure I have the latest
versions of the files
and as I'm telling you, let's wait for
one or two to be made.
And let's see,
while it's being generated, as
we discussed in the previous class, in the
intermodular project, well, of
course, what I
hope is that in your heads, well,
now the concept of
what resources are going to begin to germinate  It's necessary, eh, for
the project you're setting up, not just
for a project for business management systems
, but for what
your intermodular project is going to be.
What resources, what needs,
what costs? Okay, obviously in the
previous class I was, let's see,
dramatizing a bit, I was exaggerating
a bit, because one thing I've been
telling you is how many
software licenses you have to sell, but
you yourselves should have
told me another perspective, another solution
for the same problem, okay? What
solution would you tell me? Let's see, reload.
And no, not at the moment.
What solution would you tell me? By the way,
how's the RAM?
Good, it's there.
Okay. What solution would you tell me? This is what I was
telling you before, Fran, about 8.7
GB, of which I ca
n't see right now the memory that
Oyama uses,
but well, obviously it
has to be somewhere around here
or calls.
Let's see, reload.
Oh, very good. Okay, error calling
Olama,
okay? Timed out.  What does time
out mean? Just a moment. It means that
generally when we call Oyama
we have a limit. Let's see,
stream headers. The limit is usually 120.
Let's put limit.
Uh, stream headers. No headers.
Documentation.
Uh, doc.
Hm.
Limit,
no. Well,
here time out 120. Well, I don't want a
limit of, I'll tell you 600 like I'll tell you
6,000. I mean, I don't care how long it takes,
but do it. The limit of 120 is fine. It's just
that if it hasn't done it in 2 minutes,
we assume there's been some problem,
maybe it's fallen into an infinite loop and
what we do is break that
infinite loop and exit.
I insist, it seems very good to me, but
okay, we don't want that. We want, in this
case, we know we're giving it a
pro, we want to give it time. Okay,
so, ah, VLLM, yes, yes, yes, I know, I know
, I know.
Yes, the thing about VLLM is that it doesn't  It's not just
for using the GPU, but also for
distributing, okay? But for using
a farm of computers and distributing
the load among them and, obviously,
using as many resources as possible,
okay? Whether it's a GPU or whatever they
have. Yes, yes, I haven't tried it
yet, but these days I'm going in
and out and looking at documentation and
watching tutorials because indeed,
Fran, that is the next step, okay? And it
's that, okay, I already have it working on
one computer, okay? I already see what I can
do and also, obviously, I see the
limitations, but also related
to what we're talking about in
distributed computing processes and services and
parallel computing. Well, okay, but
now, what happens if I have a set of
computers that I can use for the
calculation? Well, yes, Fran, yes, yes, yes,
obviously, obviously I have it, I've
looked at it, I haven't
tested it yet, but yes, I have
indeed looked at
distributing calculations across many computers and
so on.
And let's see, reloading here is going to take a
while, I estimate, but as I tell you,  As long as it
generates the first one, then it's fine for us.
Okay, I was asking you about the
intermodular project.
What's the
strategy you didn't tell me about? Okay,
I said strategy number one, uh,
analyzing how many licenses you have to
sell and how much you have to sell the
ticket for. But what's the other
strategy? What do you say? I
'll take a moment.
Intermodular project
and analysis, not design
and resource determination, exercises.
And not here,
here.
What do you say?
What do you think?
Let's see, I'll tell you. We were
talking before, while this is computing,
by the way, we'll check that it works.
Okay. We've been talking about €80,000,
€80,000, we've been talking about
€8,000 licenses per year, which
could be if the software justifies it,
if the software features
justify it. Or if we're talking about
invoicing software with Verifactu,
well, a standard one, 720,112 licenses.
This is one way,
but now I ask you, the other way,
especially when you start a
project, is, tell me, answer me,
how could we cut costs?
What do you say? I
mean,
we set up a company.
Previously, we assumed that
since we provided 24/7
IT support, we haven't
talked about Saturdays and
Sundays, but anyway,
€10,000 in salaries for three
IT technicians.
Uh, so it came to €60,000 or €50,000, something like
€1,000 as a base. Okay? What do you say
about that?
Of course, what you should tell me.
Let's see how this goes. Not at the moment.
Okay, let's see, follow the monitor. Okay,
it's option two.
If the economic estimate
is very high, it's very strong,
uh, let's reduce the
necessary resources
to the minimum
to be able to
start the business.
So, what does that mean? Well,
a developer
develops,
implements,
starts
a developer, that same
Developer.
Of course, it's pushing at the beginning. That
same developer does the support,
and let's see,
let's see,
let's see for a moment.
Of course, the same marketing campaign has to be
done, maybe a
hired salesperson.
Well, marketing campaign, okay?
Server, of course, it depends on what we're
going to set up.
Okay, office or maybe a server at
home, your own server.
So, uh, your own equipment, your
own server, it
won't be very powerful
if you assign yourself
a salary. Of course, if you assign yourself a
salary of €0, then obviously the
cost of setting it up is €0. Okay,
but I insist,
uh, let's say you don't get paid, but
let's say your computer breaks down. So
then a €1,000 computer.
Okay,
let's say you have a computer, but
imagine that the computer breaks down,
okay? No problem. A server of the
€1,000 in development equipment
and the server.
And now I'll tell you, look at the question I'm
going to ask you.
So, you
assign yourself a salary,  Okay?
And yes, yes, yes, correct. The same way
we implement
artificial intelligence to get rid of
cumbersome processes that we don't like, such as
software documentation, we
can also implement it to
do, in other words, to automate what is
called the design and creation of
marketing and communication materials.
Yes, I mean, of course, of course.
Now we're talking about that. Now we're talking about
that too.
Uh, let's see. Development team,
server. Okay, I was honestly saying,
what salary could you assign yourselves? So
that if it's too high or bad
because the budget goes up, but if it's
too low, okay? I insist, be
honest because after x months
working for too low a salary,
you yourselves will say, "Look, it happened, I
earn more picking fruit in the
field." Okay? And you'll leave the project at
1300 minimum, okay? I don't know, I'm
telling you, uh, no, there's no correct answer here
, it's whatever you
say,  "Hey, if I win this, even if I'm
fighting the elements, at
least it's worth it, okay?  1300 €
for 12 months."
That means that
calculator
and 12 * 1300 are 15,000.
plus 1000 of development equipment plus
1000 of server are, let's say 18,000.
Total of 18,000
€ budget.
Of course, we have lowered from 80,000 to 18,000
1000. And if we establish,
supposedly, that licenses
cost
720 €.
Okay, then 18,000,
okay? Yes, yes, for that reason, but you adjust the
money, but you also cannot give yourself a
salary of 200 € that you yourself in 6
months say, "Look, it's that I ca
n't do it anymore.  You know?  It's just that life doesn't
give me anything.  Okay, then let's see.
Uh, 17,600 gives birth to 720.
So instead of having to sell
112 licenses, you would have to sell
25 licenses.
You'd have to sell 25 licenses
to get to 1.0, right?
For a start.
achieve
profitability
in the sense that you are left with
zero, but you are left with zero, but you have
earned €10,000 a month.  So, you don't
save, your assets don't increase,
but at least you had a salary
of €1,500 and you didn't go bankrupt.  Okay?
So this is what I want you to
think about for your project.  This is
what you have to do in your
project, which is basically defining it
for your whatever you want to
do.  Okay?  Good.  Next question.
Hey, let's see.  There is some documentation design here
.  We'll talk a little bit
about this later, but wait a minute.
Professional activities.
Okay, business area.  Okay, Fran, I'm going to
jump straight here to the topic of the
commercial area and we're going to jump
directly to what you've commented.
Okay, let's go to new folder 001
basic contents
and 00
two exercises.
Okay, there's a discipline
within marketing
called, Let's see how this goes, by the
way, let's see if it's done anything.
Let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see.  Oh wow,
super cool,
super cool.  Dependency and relationships with
other files.  What do you think?  Okay,
so this file is the
main entry point for
José Vicente's RP application.  Okay, cool.  Role of the
global project.  Authentication,
main interface, session start,
session verification.  Fantastic.  Okay, so,
even though it's going to cost a fortune to
generate all the complete documentation, it
might take 48 hours to get it working,
but at least we know that it's going to
produce documentation that's first tailored
to each file and second contextual to the
project.  Okay?  Let's leave it there for a
while longer, calculating, okay?  So, so
, yeah, yeah, yeah, right, right, Fran.
There, there you are absolutely right.  Okay, yes, it
is possible to have a portfolio of
recurring clients in the sense that, uh, there
is a maxim in marketing.  Then
there are people who agree with this
maxim, there are people who
disagree more, who say that it costs
three times as much to acquire a new client as it does to
retain an existing one, right?  It's
a phrase that is said in marketing.
So basically, basically what
the phrase means is that,
well, it's what you say, okay?  The
important thing is to build a portfolio
of clients to whom you
can then sell more products,
right?  Well, I was telling you, I was telling you that
here in exercises
marketing and
communication materials.
Okay, so I'm always going to go to the BOE
, the BOE BOE marketing and
advertising.  And in the BOE Fran, I think you'll
find inspiration there
about what activities to do.
Development of marketing and
communication materials.  Materials development,
design and development, sorry, design and
development
of marketing and
communications materials.  1007.
Code 1007. Look, you know what?
I'm going to stick this to you.
This is index.
Opa.  Oh,
come on.
No.
Index.Md
from here.  Let's see, I'm going to leave out
economic management,
but not because it's not important, which is
very important, but because I'm not
going to tell you this,
Pila Ruiz is going to tell you this, obviously.
This is very important, this is very
important, this is very important.  This
is very important, okay?  This is very
important.  I'm going to take this away from you
mainly because Alicia is telling you this.
This is a project, this is F. And this is
training in workplaces.  Okay?
Now, in each subject we're
going to cover a little bit, so that
obviously we won't have time to
learn the entire marketing and
advertising cycle in half an hour or an
hour, but it will give us time to at
least get an idea of ​​what
marketing does and get ideas.  So I
come over here and I say, let's go to
1007.
Okay.  And in code 1007
what I'm going to do is I'm
going to take
the syllabus here and paste it for you.
And no, this is
the index, okay?  And this is
here.
What should be done?  Well, then,
create advertising materials,
taking into account the composition, the
color, the typography, okay?  Writing,
laying out press ads, composing
elements,
managing visual perception,
balance, tension, and
reading sense.  Okay?  Good.  Okay.  Okay.
Application of persuasive communication techniques
,
that is, communication that
suggests to the customer that he/she, that is,
invites him/her to buy.  Okay?  Okay.  What else
is important?
Let's see.  Okay.  Development of
advertising materials,
design for multimedia presentations,
emails, email marketing,
press releases, okay?  Tools for making
presentations.
Okay.  Okay, cool.
Well, what else do we have?  What else do
we have?  Important, important.
Marketing policies.
Where are you?  Come on, here.
Okay, marketing policies,
market opportunity assessment,
and
here
marketing policies
md.
What will we talk about at a given time?
Well, for the evaluation of
business opportunities.
Here, in services marketing
, how do we define our
product policy?  We are programmers, we do
n't know that there is a
product policy, but what product policy does
our service have?  Well, we have to
start thinking that this exists.  Okay.
Hey, let's see for a moment.  Definition
of pricing policy.  What
pricing policies exist?
How do I set the price of my
app?  What do I base this on?  Well, this
block of knowledge, which is
marketing policies, tells us that, right?
Selection of form and
distribution channel.  Fran, how are we going to
distribute our project?
Well, I have no idea, but the thing is
that we spent a whole year in
first year programming, and
in second year we continued programming.
Right now in business management systems
we're programming, but
of course, suddenly someone says to you,
"Okay, but how are you going to distribute what
you're programming?"  and you're
like, "Wow, I hadn't
thought of that."  Okay, the idea is that
theoretically someone from programming
should collaborate with someone from
marketing to create a
marketing campaign.  Of course, but it's
also important that the programmer
has a series of
marketing ideas, right?  Okay, so by the way,
we're going to go to the RP and there's no
news yet.  It hasn't exploded.
The monitor is still at full power, okay?  That
means he's still calculating
well.  What else?  What else is done in
marketing?  Okay.
Yes, correct, correct.  But that's what I
'm telling you, that is, without intermediaries,
with our own platform, okay?
Correct.  That's a means of dissemination,
launching it with marketing to the market as the
first searches on Google.  That, Fran,
is called SEO, it's called search engine
optimization, but we have to know
a little bit about SEO.  I'm not telling you to
become SEO experts, but we
do have to learn a little bit
about SEM, okay?  What you said, about
paying for searches, is done with
another type of positioning
called SEM, which is search engine
marketing.  But once again, okay? We
need to know the basics, the
foundation of how Google
AdSense, Facebook Ads, or LinkedIn Ads work
to know how to create ads on
search engines and social media.  Okay, that's what
I'm saying.
Okay, hey, digital marketing, this has
our name on it.  Okay, so let's go
this way.  Well, wait a minute.  Uh,
zero, 0931
0931 digital marketing.
Well, here in this subject,
unfortunately there is a lot of chaff.
There is a lot of straw.
And in the syllabus, I mean,
digital marketing.  Then, when it is taught in
reality,
the chaff is removed and an attempt is made to
teach it as best as possible.
But okay, internet connections, what is the
internet, how to manage
email.  Well,
electronic invoicing, that's not bad to know either.
Determining the strategy in
interrelations with other users on the
web.  Sure, IRC programs.  Wow,
IRC programs, that hasn't been used for
decades.
web page construction.  You can
imagine how much it
matters to us.  Design of the digital marketing plan
.  Okay.  Okay.
Very good.  Well, well
, what else do we have?
What else do we have?  Media and supports.
Let's see.
media and communication supports 004
MD.
Oh, stay.  Obviously, as you
can imagine, what I'm going to do next
is I'm going to take this, I'm
going to pass it on to GPT chat or
whoever, and I'm going to say, "Give me an
explanation of each of these things."
Let's see.
In fact, in fact, I think I'm going to
do it here now with you.
Yes, Fran.  Let's see, that's where I want to get to.  Very
good.  Okay, that's what I
want to talk to you about.   Of
course, in this case, what do we do?
On the one hand, we're seeing that there's
a lot of content to cover,
so if we hire someone,
we'll increase the budget again,
which obviously would be the case if we paid
someone to do it well.  Okay,
but we're increasing the
budget again.
The other way, Fran, is we do it
ourselves, but if we do it ourselves
we have to learn how to do it.
What would you say is the
correct answer?  There's no right answer,
okay?  But, but, where would you say I'm
going?  Well, what I'm getting at is the
same thing I told you a moment ago,
and that is that we would most likely have to
, first of all, at
first, do it ourselves.  And to
do that, we have to have a
certain idea of ​​what needs to be done, and
then, obviously, when we
want to take the leap, we have to
have someone from the
marketing and advertising cycle who can
dedicate themselves specifically to that task, and
you can dedicate yourself specifically
to programming, right?  That's kind of the
point.  So eh let's see.  Well,
public relations and
event planning.
Well, computer scientists aren't really into
events, to be honest, but okay,
why not?
At least let's see that this exists.
Let's see.
Okay.
And public relations.
Okay, next up is
business research.  This is very
important
that this is 100.
Commercial research.
And
here.
Okay, so
what is the market?  What are the limits of
the market for your
chosen product?
What is the macroenvironment?  What is the
microenvironment,
studying
consumer behavior?
All of these are things that are
very difficult for us programmers to understand,
but of course, you suddenly, yes, I mean, you
take any point from the
marketing agenda, just this one,
just this one, at some point, since
you've known me, we've talked, we've
even dealt with this concept that popped
into our heads of studying
consumer behavior.
I mean, never.  I've talked to you about
databases, markup languages,
programming, operating systems,
servers,
but of course, now that we want to sell a
product, imagine how important it
is—I've just underlined a sentence,
okay?—which is to study how
our consumer behaves.
Horrible, I mean, horrible.  It's like,
gosh, we've been learning one
thing, but we haven't been learning
another, right?  Because?  because it's another
cycle, okay?  This is from the
marketing and advertising cycle, but of course,
when we have to start
designing a product, all those
kinds of things are important.  11
fieldwork in
commercial research and 007
pun md
And what else do we have?
Product launch.
Okay.  Hey, new file
008, product
and service launch
dot MD.
Oh, the sea.  Oh, sir.
Okay,
fine.  And finally,
customer,
consumer and user service.
MD
subject 1110.
Ay.
Okay,
let's test
the system a little.  So far I've copied a
series of contents for you so we can start
reviewing, but what do you think
if I then say, "Okay, now, but
empathy, what's this about?
Assertiveness, what's this about?
Nonverbal communication. But
what's this about? Well, once again what I
can do is
create a small Python file that
documents all of this, that gives me at
least a small description and that
allows me to generate a
series of small notes to begin with, okay? So
to do that,
let's see, I come here, I come
here, okay? I create a new file and
say
Python script
calling to oama
gema or
yama
to read a bunch of MD files
in a folder in the same folder
as
script
first feed
them all at once toama
to get context
and then feed
line by line
each of the documents
to query description
in Spanish
[Music]
to make something
like a documentation
save
resulting
documents
besides
original docum
may
with a
file name extension, okay?
Uh, sample file is this.
So,
moment.
lines
starting
with, no, how do you say hyphen? How do you
say hyphen in English?
It's no, no, that type of hyphen, okay?
With no hyphen starting with hyphen
are eh top level topics,
lines starting
with hen
are subtopics.
And I think I have around here, I think I
have around here, I've seen one
that had like a third level of
subtopics.
Now, to annoy, it won't appear.
Well, no, if it doesn't appear, it doesn't
appear.
Look here.
Okay,
these
lines starting
with a dot
are third
level subtopics
and I think that's it.
Let's see.
In this case, I'm not saying quen. I think
here I would have to use the OSS model,
that is, GPT OSS, because here I need a
strong model, okay? But well,
in this case I'm telling it that it either
calls or gems, because they are
models that are, how should I put it? Uh,
for general use, okay?
The Quen model is the model for
programming,
but obviously, well, it does
n't apply in this case.
Okay?  Build a global context,
go through it line by line,
use gem or flame. I think I have these
two.
Okay. And here we go.
Meanwhile,
meanwhile, let's see if the Where
are you? Let's
see if the RPMD has made any progress.
And header
or timeout. Okay, okay. Timeout. Okay, I
have to give it more time because if
it starts with a timeout, it's probably
going to time out forever.
I'm going to stop it,
but I would have to give it a time limit
of more than infinity, okay? So
that way, so that it takes all the time it
needs. Okay, so I'm
going to do Python summaries here,
okay? And in summaries, punch
a moment.
Okay, let's try it out.
What happens is that
make this
stream contents
so that
files are
written
as they are generated don't have to
wait
for a
contents.
Once again, since waiting for the
entire document will cost a fortune, in that
case what we're going to do is tell it
okay, to do real streaming.
Stream each chunk, okay? So, well,
that's how we'll see it and so on.  Let's
see it. You'll see the docd point. Ah, okay.
Okay, okay. Fantastic.
Let's see it
. Let's see. Let's
see, wait a moment.
Okay,
okay. Let's see. And uh, documentation
over here. Okay, we've got this
clear. Let's go to second, let's go to
intermodular project, let's go to lines of
action, let's go to, hey,
uh, sorry,
to professional activities. Let's go to the
commercial area,
okay? Let's open summaries. I
'm scared. Let's see what happens, because of
course, let's see, uh, Python 3,
summaries,
the best.
What?
How?
How? Let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see.
Okay, okay
, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. Okay,
okay.
Let's see.
Please help me list.
[Music]
Although
you know them,
also make sure the script processes
only MD files. Let's see.
Okay.
Only pure
MD files
and not.doc.mdfiles to not
.
E, how would this be? Gee, right? The
word
to not  process recursibili
own files.
Okay, the thing is that chat GPT knows
exactly which models I have
installed on my computer, especially
because chat GPT helped me
install them.
So if it's not the Yama
Instruct, then it'll be another one
we have. Let's see.
Okay.
Okay,
let's see list the models
. Okay
. Okay. The best available. Oh,
wait. Let's
see, first,
first this over here. Second,
obviously. Okay. Okay
.
Okay,
let's see, I
'm going to go to this one.
Okay, I have these.
Which one is it? Okay, of course, if it takes the
best one and this one, it's going to crash my
computer,
and of course, I don't want it, I do
n't want it, or I do want it. I mean, it
crashes, meaning it leaves me
unresponsive for an hour or so,
but of course, and it seems like it's going to burn out.
Okay, close the door.
Okay, then
let's see.
Your script already excludes.
Okay, default preferred. Let's go for
this. I like this better.
Okay.
Okay.  Default preferred.
Default preferred. Ah, look how good.
Okay. Okay. And now def autopick,
okay? And def autopick.
Okay.
Okay, now we load,
we load
this one here.
We run the model.
Okay, this is something else. Wow. Quen. What do you mean
quen? No,
no, it
was this one.
Well, let's see. But
the one that took me wasn't the favorite one
on the list, but okay. I
'm going to ask.
list is this but
then it
shouldn't have taken llama in first place. It shouldn't have taken llama
.
Let's see if the document is
streaming.
And ah, index. Oops, I hadn't counted that.
Okay, okay. Uh, let's see.
Okay. Uh, wow.
Okay, cool,
cool.
And in fact it is streaming. It's true
that it is streaming.
Wow.
Oh, oh, oh, oh. Reload. Yes, it is
streaming. Yes. Okay, okay. Very good.
Hey, let's see the answer.
Hey, here
your writing is looking for an
exact match. Ah.
Wow.
Okay. Okay, so default prefer.
Okay, it's reloading. It's still
doing pretty well, really, but
come on, come on. Hey, summaries. The default
prefer. I take this and now in Autopic
Model
I put this.
Autopic model. I take this,
stop,
delete the one that doesn't work for me, I
didn't count on that, but oh well.
Okay, this doesn't exist outside. And we
run it again to see what it picks up. It picks
Quen again. Well, whatever. Okay, so let's
leave it with Quen. How strange.
Good. So index,
the main objective of, okay? Okay,
if you notice, it's
writing it little by little.
Let's see it.
Now.
Okay, well
, wait a moment and let's see, let's
wait a moment for the index to finish
because what I want is to see how it enters
each of
the subjects. and it starts making a
comment for each of the
subpoints.
And now, obviously,
obviously, it will
take as long as it takes. By the way,
since we're at it, Fran, because of what
you were saying before about the VLM,
uh, how can I make oama use GPU?
Because it's using the CPU.
Let's see.
Okay, I have...
No, well, as I told you, I don't know what the
problem is, but on this computer I
used it on the GPU
and nothing, and now it's not using the
GPU, but okay.
Let's see how we're doing.
Reload.
Okay,
digital marketing is the discipline that
deals with the main objectives.
Okay. Okay
. Okay
.
Well, now we'll finish, but as
I told you, I'm in no rush.
Obviously, I want to leave this
computing tonight to let you know when
you have it, so that you can download it and
see it, and you can
use the script for whatever you want,
obviously.
And the goal is that in future
classes, we'll have a little bit of a view of
the marketing content at the
moment when we want to make an
application that sells and in the  moment
in which in the intermodular project we not
only want to mix the different
modules, which we obviously want that,
but also what we want is uh to
obtain an integral sales process,
that is, hm consider the launch
of a service. Not only from the point of
view of programming and the
database and the markup languages,
etc., etc., but from the point
of view of knowing the user, the
client, knowing the market and having an
idea that what we are going to launch
will fit well in the
market.
I'm going to do one thing. I'm going to do one
thing. I'm going to cheat a little. Okay, I'm
going to cheat a little because I'm
a little impatient.
And Okay. Good. And then and then uh I'm
going to close here, I'm going to
delete this and then I'm
going to move the index to 101
or 100, with which it will move to the
very bottom. And then I'm going to
here I'm going to start with
marketing and communication materials.
And then yes, now yes,
now yes.
Okay, you'll see how,
well, I have for the moment  Level three.
Okay, let's see it.
And what I want is to see how you're going to give me
a
comment on each of the units.
Let's see it.
Yes, yes, correct,
correct. And that, Fran, is our
opportunity
because,
uh, the objective, if you notice, the objective
in the previous development is very
specific for programmers, is to
automate documentation, okay? No one
outside of programming understands how
disgusting that work is, but what I
'm doing now is a
much more normal world automation
, okay? It's much more of the
world, let's say, applicable to any
type of person or any type of
business
and it's not that difficult, okay? But it's not
that difficult, Fran, for us, because
for us, because we know how to do
much more complex things, for
us it's a business opportunity
for what we were talking about before, as in
the case of Salva Moret, it's to automate,
okay? To help people automate
and therefore make
artificial intelligence, instead of being
or in addition to being a threat to our
work, become a complement to
our  Work, okay? Let it be
another business opportunity. There's a lot of talk
on social media about whether
artificial intelligence is taking over the work
of juniors and not the work of
seniors. Okay, I don't know, maybe it is, but
the truth is that a senior isn't going to
start doing what I just
did. This, which is an automation of
a document, is a job for juniors.
Okay? So what I create here is
reload. Now, now. This is what
I want, okay? This is what I want,
and correct, exact, exact, correct.
Okay, that kind of micro. Exactly. That's what I was
going to tell you. I mean, I was going to
tell you that phrase, okay? That phrase about,
well, there's something complex to do, and you
integrate automation, and that
automation helps the client
make a good decision. That's a
good implementation in that
first, a junior will do that,
a senior will decide, but
a junior will do it, and it's not taking
anyone's work away, I mean, no one would read it.
That client, the thousands, thousands of
lines of description, okay? So,
I agree with you there that those types
of implementations, I think they are
good AI implementations and it's that
AI does something that until now you couldn't
do. It doesn't take anyone's work away, it
doesn't take anyone's cake away, and it helps
people. Okay.
Fine. Well, nothing, now later, okay?
Reload here. Let's see. Okay,
there it is. Okay.
Okay. Offline sources. Wait a minute, wait
a minute, wait a minute. Let's see.
Preparation. Online information sources
. Search engines.
Okay. Sources.
Ah, search engines. Rules of use.
Correct, correct. Okay, okay. I'm
making sure. Yes, it's true that, uh, for
example, AI can always hallucinate and
can freak out. I was making sure it
wasn't skipping sections,
but skipping sections is more
typical of GPT chat, etc., than IAS
in local mode. I mean, GPT chat a lot of the
time  It's clear that they skip things to
save resources. On the other hand, with
local IAS, if you tell them to do
something, they won't stop until they do it. They'll
do it better or worse,
because obviously due to a
power issue, let's see how the CPU performs, due to a
power issue they'll do worse than
the GPT model, but okay, but they'll
do it until the end.
Okay, so nothing, I'll upload all
this later, okay? I figure I'll
stop it in a while and
put it back up tonight. Uh, also this
weekend Fran synced what we
talked about before, about these,
the test I deleted because it came out
badly, and the one where I deleted the evaluation
because it came out zero and nothing, and over the
weekend I'll re-upload the evaluations
along with what I was telling you before,
right? That the evaluations were
redoing the prompt so that it evaluates
more fairly.
Uh, what was I going to tell you? Stay
tuned. I think the email I'm going
to send  I'm going to send it with a copy to you,
okay? So I can put
you and Salva in direct communication so
he can contact you and call you and talk, okay? And I'm telling you, I think what I'm going to say is, "Hey, maybe I'll send Luis too, I don't know." Okay, but in a way like, hey, see? Talk,
uh,
explain everything to him, explain
everything you need to explain to him, let
him ask you everything I need to
ask you, okay? Because as I told you,
last time I sent him a guy who
turned out to be really dumb and this time I want to
send him someone who's powerful,
okay? But as I told you, I don't want to
send someone who's a slave.
It's just that when you meet that guy and
when that guy tells you everything he
does and everything he's involved in, you'll see
that you're interested in being in contact with
that guy, okay? That's why, I mean, I don't
think of it as a relationship of, I don't have to
compensate that guy because  This was
3 years ago, I haven't had any contact with him.
I mean, I don't have any
need, but what, I mean, I want to
send you because the possibilities of
two-way benefit are quite
large, but well, as I said, you see,
meet him, do the interview, you're not
obligated to anything and that's it. In fact,
notice that his email, his email, well, it
's really more or less the same. I
mean, without any kind of commitment, I
wanted to ask you, yes and such. I mean,
he's not telling me, "Hey, man,
send me someone because you sent me
a guy who was really weak." Okay, yes, he
mentions it and it's true. Okay, it doesn't
work perfectly well as you
know, correct. And such. Okay, well, that's it. Well, that's not
much else for today. Now I'll start
uploading videos to the platform and
updating the medium screen. And that's it,
see you on Monday. Yesterday they told me
that there
's a long weekend, okay? That Thursday
is October 9th, I didn't count on it
and on
Friday they told me that it's a long weekend,
Which is a huge pain, but
hey, it is what it is. Okay? Then,
well, nothing, I don't know. Look, it also
depends a bit on whether I
have my son on Thursday or Friday or not, because if I don't have
my son, well, it doesn't matter. Hey, do you know if you
're with Mom or with me next week
?
October 9th and 10th, Thursday and
Friday, which is a holiday, right? Okay, well,
nothing, well, once I know,
because if I have my son, well, nothing,
but if my wife is going to have him, well, I'll
tell you, hey, we'll take some classes
and we won't miss a beat, we don't go a
week without classes on processes and
data access and this and
business management systems, which,
damn, it's just on
Thursday and Friday, the holiday. I'm telling you, they
told me yesterday. Yesterday they told me,
"Hey, next week." And I was
like, "What?"  What, what bridge?
What long weekend?" And of course, then you start doing the
math and you say, "Damn,
October 9th." I didn't remember that was already
there. Okay? So, well, I'll
tell you, when I know something, well, I'll tell you, and
if you have availability and you're in
Valencia and you're not going to
travel there, then we'll do at least some classes
, okay? And we won't be stuck on
content for a week.
Well, see you on Monday anyway,
okay? Come on, guys, see you now. Have a good
weekend. M.